import 'package:quiz_app/models/questions_model.dart';

List<QuestionsModel> questionsList = [
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'Which component allows us to specify the distance between widgets on the screen ?',
    choices: [
      'A. SafeArea',
      'B. SizedBox',
      'C. table',
      'D. AppBar',
    ],
    answer: 'B. SizedBox',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'Which widget type allows you to modify its appearance dynamically according to user input ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Flutter run',
      'B. Flutter build',
      'C. Flutter doctor',
      'D. Flutter help',
    ],
    answer: 'C. Flutter doctor',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'Which release mode will not contain any debugging data when run ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Profile',
      'B. Debug',
      'C. Release',
      'D. Test',
    ],
    answer: 'B. Debug',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'What language is Flutter\'s rendering engine primarily written in ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Kotlin',
      'B. C++',
      'C. Dart',
      'D. Java',
    ],
    answer: 'B. C++',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'What is a drawback of Flutter that might lead you to choose another solution ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Non-native looking application UI',
      'B. Large application footprint',
      'C. A relatively unproven framework and language',
      'D. All of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'D. All of the above',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: 'Flutter supports desktop application development.',
    choices: [
      'A. True',
      'B. False',
    ],
    answer: 'A. True',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: 'What widget would you use for repeating content in Flutter ?',
    choices: [
      'A. ExpandedView',
      'B. ListView',
      'C. Stack',
      'D. ArrayView',
    ],
    answer: 'B. ListView',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'Flutter teams are inherently more difficult to manage because the framework is so new.',
    choices: [
      'A. True',
      'B. False',
    ],
    answer: 'B. False',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: 'Flutter developed by ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Oracle',
      'B. Facebook',
      'C. Google',
      'D. IBM',
    ],
    answer: 'C. Google',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: 'Flutter is not a language; it is an SDK.',
    choices: [
      'A. True',
      'B. False',
    ],
    answer: 'A. True',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: 'The first alpha version of Flutter was released in ?',
    choices: [
      'A. 2016',
      'B. 2017',
      'C. 2018',
      'D. 2019',
    ],
    answer: 'B. 2017',
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question:
        'Flutter is mainly optimized for 2D mobile apps that can run on ?',
    choices: [
      'A. Android',
      'B. iOS',
      'C. Both A and B',
      'D. None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'C. Both A and B',
  ),
];
